妈的 Ted!
Damn it,Ted!
别再转变话题 你太过分了
You quit trying to change the\nsubject. You crossed the line.
你们合伙伤害了那可怜人的心
You are complicit in breaking\nsome poor guy's heart.
而你 是所有人里最明白其中滋味的
And you, you of all people\nknow exactly how that feels.
- 你真的不想说裤子糗事 对不?\n- 啥?
- You really don't want to tell the pants story,do you?\n- What?
裤子 裤子 裤子 裤...
Pants,pants,pants,pants,pants,\npants,pants, pants,pants,p-p...
好吧! 好
Fine! Okay?
然后 Lily来办公室帮我送裤子..
So,Lily came down to the\noffice to bring me my pants...
那她为啥要这么做?
And why did she have to do that?
因为我忘带裤子了
Because I forgot my pants.
Lily 你在这干吗?
Lily,what are you doing here?
我来给Marshal送点东西
Oh,I'm here to give Marshall something.